i thought they didn't need me anymore
i thought i could leave
and the server will continue to flourish
continue to survive
i was wrong
my time away has proved that the server
can't be without a hero
without me
since my departure a ghost-like fish has
lurked in the background
plotting scheming
who knows what they have planned
crime on the server continues to rise
and the authorities are doing nothing
about it
and worst of
all
worst of all
i have been usurped
reports have reached me that a new
vigilante has surfaced on the hermograph
server
someone of equal strength and power to
myself
duck woman
there can only be one bird-based hero on
this server
this leads me to conclude that duck
woman is nothing more than a feathered
menace her quack-based powers will bring
the server to mild frustration
and that's something i cannot allow
poultry man must return
i
must return
[Music]
that's right everyone poultry man has
officially returned i think it's time
and because it's time i have upgraded
and updated the poultry cave check it
out this place was getting seriously
neglected for a long time so much so
that there was cobwebs everywhere but
we've tidied it up we've built some
stuff and we've given it all a little
bit of an update and this is awesome
i've also moved it from outside of this
egg all the way over here so
if we take a look there's actually quite
a few people online
and i think it's time that poultry man
made an official return and here's the
beautiful thing everyone oh man it feels
good it feels good it feels good to be
back in the mask
here's the thing mumbo jumbo is actually
streaming right now
and that means we're gonna get a good
reaction and that means i know exactly
where he is
so let's go and let's go and find him
shall we oh wait i totally need to stock
up on some eggs
yeah i think that's probably enough eggs
all right let's get out of here now
while we're on our way to mumbo jumbo
i've got to announce something really
really cool i have updated my merch
store i've got poultry man t-shirts on
the merch store after months and months
of people asking for some t-shirts and
we've also got some sahara merch as well
which is awesome so look at this we got
some sahara t-shirts people have been
asking for this so much that they
actually made their own designs at one
point so it's getting a bit nuts really
so there's a link to the merch store in
the description down below and if you do
decide to pick up a t-shirt just so you
know it definitely supports me well
um me not poultry man it supports me
mumbo is at his witch farm which means
i'm i get lost in here every time
where's the exit this has something to
do with it i'm sure you know what i'm
gonna hold the totem of undying just in
case because we're not wearing
particularly good armor we're wearing
leather armor as poultry man so becoming
the chicken is extremely dangerous
during the game of demise look at that
that's some heavy damage mumbo has no
idea what's going to hit him let's see
if we can sneak in he's clearly doing
something here
i don't know what he's doing i can see
his stream so i know where he is but i
don't know what he's up to
let's see if we can sneak in
okay there he is over there let's get
ourselves in the air without him
noticing lots of chickens he's probably
got some machine that doesn't want
doesn't need lots of chickens in it
what's he making
i don't think he's actually noticed me
yet
oh no he's seen me he's definitely seen
me
it's been too long
it turns out that mumbo actually didn't
see me at all until seconds before he
finished his stream look that is it
that's all i'm gonna livestream today
i'm chillin
i'm done so that's pretty wild anyway i
i really do hope that you enjoyed this
live stream it's been a lot of fun it's
been cool chilling out
there's a man with the chicken head yep
i definitely wasted my time anger scared
him away the power of poultry i'm just
gonna clear these up just in case i
think he's making an iron farm
well let's see whoa do you see that on
the tab list jeven and scar
have demised that's not good
that's not good at all
if jevin if jevin and scar are demised
that means there's five people
on the dead team that's that's not in
our favor
on the other hand that's a lot less
competition well i've got all these eggs
so maybe we can go and find the others
it'd be a shame to waste them wait
what's this free potions for members of
the breath over death sweet is that does
that mean alive people or is that a
specific team
i'm guessing it's alive but i'll take
i'll take some i'll take something
especially a fire resistance potion holy
moly we're gonna spy on the dead team to
see what they're up to of course green's
not doing this it's it's poultry man so
it's it's it's all good it's all good
now the place that the dead like to hang
out is probably the graveyard that's
what i've been seeing i'm not sure
exactly where it is though it's a hermit
halloween district that's this is it so
this is where i might expect the dead to
be hanging out
spooky
man
the fact that this is season six second
halloween
is absolutely crazy this was started
last year and obviously halloween has
already come and gone but it's just so
perfect for the dead team to hang out in
let's see let's see if there's a scar or
a jeff in here since they're both dead
oh oh he's there chill run run run run
dive he went oh look at that mist how
awesome is that fog
okay wait wait let's focus focus focus
we have to find scar all right where is
he
there he is
and that creeper looks like he might go
for him wait have the dead been making
graveyards for themselves oh no
he's right he's definitely running from
that creeper isn't it this is i don't
even have to do anything
we don't even have to do anything we
could just sit here and watch the dead
have a hard time
this is
this is probably the most entertainment
we're gonna get
oh wait i think he's evie oh oh oh bail
fail bail no i'm not gonna save you oh
wait i subbed uh i suppose i am the hero
of this server
incoming get out of here this is the
only way i know how to fight
[Laughter]
this is not how i expected this to go
hmm i don't think eggs do damage you are
safe
the citizen
who i have never met good day
day
we truly are the hero that no one asked
for it doesn't look like the dead have
actually got any sort of base here by
the looks of things i was really
expecting the dead to have i don't know
some kind of mansion
but it looks like this is just their
graves
wait
they aren't all dead are they or is this
from before
oh oh
are they waiting until they die and then
they put their heads there stay away
from him
you know this grave is going to be full
of chickens and no one's going to
understand why
my job here is done
but you didn't do anything
exactly
okay i think that is definitely enough
of being poultry man for today but
poultry man is officially back and
how he's going to interact with the
hermits during demise i'm not sure if
green dies does poultry man die hmm
that's a question as you guys saw from
my introduction today a mysterious
character has appeared on the
hermitcraft server
and i'm not sure who it is now duck
woman was last seen at stress's base now
i don't think duck woman can necessarily
be stressed it i mean it doesn't have to
be like
who's poultry man no one knows who
poultry man is so who knows who duck
woman is the identity of duck woman is
not known
i wonder where duck woman is
there's someone there i don't want to
get too close because then they'll see
me
do you see that
oh wait that's just stress
that's not duck woman that's just that's
just stress monster doing her thing
yeah there's there's no duck woman here
hmm
we'll have to keep we'll have to keep
looking and we'll have to keep an eye
out for this person if you think you
know who the identity of duck woman is
please let me know in the comments down
below
so yeah let's go ahead and pop poultry
man back in the cave
i think our good deeds and hero schedule
is complete for this episode at least
another another poultry saves the day
let's put this back
no one knows no one knows
but what do you think of this place look
how awesome this is this is such a
better
this is such an upgrade on what used to
be here however we must return to doing
green things now seeing as the dead team
are getting bigger and stronger we
really have to get our bunker at least
somewhat defended right now it's just a
shell
wait a minute oh wait there's three
potions here as well well we'll can
observe i'm pretty sure observers would
be able to detect that i should have
checked if this was hooked up to
anything thankfully it was a genuine
present because that could have been the
end of us
okay so i think this has definitely been
a gift from someone but look at this
look at that why is someone marked is
that marking us for death
of any of the other shops got this no
okay so someone's put
uh some sort of skull and crossbones
above sahara
what on that's really ominous that's
really quite scary
i don't know what this means though
i hope i hope someone hasn't trapped
sahara oh man don't uh i shouldn't
really be giving anyone ideas because
trapping sahara
yeah that's bound to get someone
no i think there's nothing in particular
wrong here i don't know
that's really weird anyway let's head
down into the bunker and see what we can
do next oh no no no no this is the
second time i've done this i need my key
card i have to remember key card
if i forget the key card i die
so let's take a look at this place
what we've got
is a pretty good start to our bunker our
demise bunker that's going to keep us
safe and what we've got also is a link
up to
mumbo's bunker now surprisingly
mumbo has actually survived i would have
thought he would be one of the first to
go
but he's not
so what we should do
is kind of link these up a little bit
better than they are because mumbo's
mumbo's made the most
the longest tunnel in the game so far
it's horrible it's really horrible and i
don't i don't plan on using it it'd just
be i mean that's that's a pretty good
way of making sure that i'm not going to
his bunker make the longest most boring
tunnel that has ever been made in
hermitcraft
so yeah as long as we link this up
i don't see any issues with that
although we could probably make it a bit
more secret than we have
but what are we gonna do in here that's
the question we've got this bunker we've
kind of protected it with the entrance
trap
what do we do here well i was actually
thinking what if we made a bunker
within a bunker
one that only we know about
so
let's try and work with that shall we
what we could do
is make another entrance here hidden
with pistons and another key card that
goes here i mean this is going to be
crazy
because the thing is most people will
know that there's a bunker here what
they won't know is my real bunker is
actually in here now this is actually
going to take quite a while to unearth
so we'll probably have to do this in a
time lapse in the next episode but i
think this is a working concept we could
do so the plan would be
we dig out this area we use this as our
official bunker with all the useful
things in it and then this is just a
bunker full of traps there's nothing
here except traps and death so if the
dead team come after us
we have a safe place and
a defense mechanism i think that that's
perfect and look at this thing the
hourglass is still going whoever's doing
this is paying a lot of attention to
detail because every time i look at this
there's a few blocks difference it's
actually kind of creeping me out
what is scar up to with this thing it's
actually really worrying me
wait that doesn't have anything to do
with this does it
this random banner i hope not but on an
unrelated note and this this is really
weird so
i'm actually going to find an area
that's actually a little away from the
island because what i plan on doing
is a charity live stream on sunday the
17th of november so apologies to those
of you watching in the future i'm pretty
sure the live stream will be up for you
to watch in the future but basically i'm
participating in a live stream that aims
to tackle climate change
and i plan on doing this using
hermitcraft or playing on the
hermitcraft server now this doesn't
really where on earth am i this is not
where i wanted to be heading in the
right direction climate change is a
massive issue and in this live stream i
want to kind of show how we can tackle
this
but oh here it is here it is in this
live stream i plan on talking about
issues related to climate change and how
we can fight it and hopefully raise some
money for the charity called love
tropics
so what i plan on doing and this is why
i'm kind of mentioning it in this video
is i want to use this village as a bit
of an example in the live stream and
we're going gonna
transform it but it doesn't really have
anything to do with our current
hermitcraft
journey so to speak so this is a bit of
a a side story that's basically going to
exist just for two days but this is a
perfect spot and this is where this is
all going to happen i should probably
try and remember where this is it took
me ages to find this place
so if you're interested in that and it's
not already gone past the 17th of
november please check out the live
stream it will be happening at 3 p.m gmt
and again apologies to those of you in
the future because it's already happened
and after this video you can go and see
that live stream if you want ah finally
okay i can make it back
it's the christmas district
i don't know if this got finished this
is so weird because season six has gone
on for so long now that we've gone full
circle just like the halloween district
this place will
suddenly become used again and it feels
really strange to be back here
especially as
oh my goodness especially as we did like
the christmas presents and stuff there
was like uh yeah over here there's a
sentence like are we gonna use this
again are we gonna do presents
are we gonna do a secret santa
if we do a secret santa i've got a
little surprise
hmm
that will be really fun oh man so i'm
guessing that this would be awesome to
come back to oh my there's many that's
like crazy
memories memories but actual memories
that happened a year ago that's really
strange anyway i want to head back to
sahara
because i want to start wrapping up this
video for you today i'm afraid it is a
little bit shorter than usual i have
been absolutely swamped so busy in real
life i found it really difficult to find
time to record too much videos
but one of the big things about this
video that i wanted to tell you was
about the sahara merch uh you can
officially shop at sahara my favorite
design of a t-shirt is this one where
you've got the shop at sahara and it's a
full flow diagram of how sahara works
and you can wear that without it
screaming minecraft too much or you
could go for our sahara logo ones as
well we've got genuine
architect
sahara merch and it's really really cool
and i'm very very happy with how that's
worked out so if you're interested in
that the link is down below but what's
really special about these t-shirts and
it kind of ties in to this live stream
that i was talking about this is a an
eco-friendly company that i'm working
with called t-mill and basically what
they do is when your t-shirt has come to
the end of its life or you stop wearing
it it has a code on it and you can scan
that code and send it back to them and
get five pounds off your next
order
so this means that they will recycle
that t-shirt once it's finished it
doesn't end up in a landfill it doesn't
get burnt it gets the materials get
reused into new t-shirts and products
helping reduce
some of the impact of fast fashion so
that's why i'm very very excited to
release this new merch store with you
today and i really hope you will take a
look at it because we've got some cool
designs and there will be some more in
the future in the very near future so
that's it for me everyone thank you very
very much for watching and i do hope you
enjoyed my little portrait man intro
good
bye